{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832553340","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832553340"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fbef75c8-bf01-49b5-95b3-56d57bc52e6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832554366","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832554366"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fbef75c8-bf01-49b5-95b3-56d57bc52e6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832559137","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832559136"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fbef75c8-bf01-49b5-95b3-56d57bc52e6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832564673","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832564672"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fbef75c8-bf01-49b5-95b3-56d57bc52e6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832570865","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832570864"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fbef75c8-bf01-49b5-95b3-56d57bc52e6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832575509","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832575508"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fbef75c8-bf01-49b5-95b3-56d57bc52e6e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832584900","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832584900"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832587312","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832587312"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832587753","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832587753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832587954","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832587953"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832588457","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832588457"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832591290","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832591290"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASUBIRI"," userResponse":" NINASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832591879","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832591878"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832592079","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832592078"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832592843","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832592843"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832595428","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832595428"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832596215","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832596215"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832599184","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832599184"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832599481","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832599481"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832599559","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832599558"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 5698289e-93c1-47b0-b458-87b66b9a7c62"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832607622","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832607622"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 990ac587-7a2a-4463-a951-5271135fd893"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-b-j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832611422","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832611422"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 990ac587-7a2a-4463-a951-5271135fd893"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_T..T.all.rand.all.stat.show.114"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-b-j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832624183","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832624183"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fb6b6bcd-4022-40e4-b1f9-63d72d8c16d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-5-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832629633","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832629633"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fb6b6bcd-4022-40e4-b1f9-63d72d8c16d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-1-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832635869","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832635869"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fb6b6bcd-4022-40e4-b1f9-63d72d8c16d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_8-9-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832641216","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832641216"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fb6b6bcd-4022-40e4-b1f9-63d72d8c16d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_0-3-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832646811","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832646811"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fb6b6bcd-4022-40e4-b1f9-63d72d8c16d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-4-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832653942","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832653942"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fb6b6bcd-4022-40e4-b1f9-63d72d8c16d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-4-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832659727","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832659727"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fb6b6bcd-4022-40e4-b1f9-63d72d8c16d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_0-6-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832666194","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832666193"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fb6b6bcd-4022-40e4-b1f9-63d72d8c16d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_6-5-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832673769","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832673769"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fb6b6bcd-4022-40e4-b1f9-63d72d8c16d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-2-0"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832679887","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832679887"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fb6b6bcd-4022-40e4-b1f9-63d72d8c16d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_2-9-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832684182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832684181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" fb6b6bcd-4022-40e4-b1f9-63d72d8c16d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_2-9-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832695281","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832695281"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832698828","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832698828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832700424","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832700424"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832704285","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832704284"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832705885","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832705884"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832709842","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832709842"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832711436","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832711435"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832715186","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832715185"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832716785","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832716785"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832736054","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832736054"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832737674","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832737674"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832741279","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832741279"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832742840","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832742840"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832746852","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832746852"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832748427","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832748426"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832752054","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832752054"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832753607","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832753607"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832764752","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832764752"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832764934","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832764934"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" bdb4fde8-b85e-4bdd-80cf-af0d8f8bd415"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832778607","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832778607"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832781996","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832781996"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" toroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832783576","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832783576"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TAUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832787339","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832787339"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tausi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832788944","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832788944"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832793734","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832793734"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tabasamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABASAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832795344","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832795344"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832799381","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832799381"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832800987","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832800986"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TRENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832814830","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832814830"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" treni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TRENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832816421","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832816420"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832820492","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832820492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tumbo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832822059","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832822059"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832825728","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832825728"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832827297","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832827296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832830840","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832830839"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832832421","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832832420"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-T.rand.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832841259","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832841259"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832841415","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832841414"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" 63f97963-5098-416f-902d-5463bf20a7de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-T.rand.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tikiti maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKITI"," userResponse":" TIKITI MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832850675","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832850675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" dc3f5036-6d8b-4d89-937f-c9f4c6ce094c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832851225","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832851224"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" dc3f5036-6d8b-4d89-937f-c9f4c6ce094c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543832852203","data":{"timestamp":" 1543832852203"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181203_064235"," gameId":" dc3f5036-6d8b-4d89-937f-c9f4c6ce094c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo kale paliishi mzee mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}